Elex Lee

Los Angeles • Phone: 408.480.8373 • E-Mail: elexlee@gmail.com

Summary

Full Stack Developer with an emphasis on *iOS front-end development*. My most recent project to date was building the Mink iOS application by myself. Previously worked in production and process control for pharmaceutical and entertainment related companies.

Technical Skills

Swift / Obj-C • PostgreSQL • JavaScript • HTML / CSS • Express • Node.js

Experience

Mink | Lead iOS Developer

Mar 2015 - Present

Application allows user to find prominent colors from images

- Took project from ideation to production using the Apple's Swift programming language
- Responsible for creating architecture and prioritizing features for Mink app based on user flow
- Features include: color sharing / printing features / saving color selections
- Used k-means clustering algorithm and buckets system for accurate color sorting

Snapvite | Full-stack Developer

Apr 2015 - Present

Intuitive and automated event creation and coordination

- Helped push v1.2 of Snapvite application (Obj-C)
- Created reminder text notification feature
- Worked with Parse database and Twilio phone messaging services
- Influenced key decisions on product design of v1.2 of Snapvite
- Used Localytics to guide and implement UI changes to user event creation flow

CustomPax Inc | Production Process Control

Oct 2014 - Dec 2014

Provide practitioners with support to formulate concern-specific formulas

- Facilitated day to day team activities
- Promoted to manage a team of 7
- Help implement new method for product creation flow
- Worked with offices overseas to maintain accurate inventory

Education

Tradecraft | Engineering

Feb 2015 - April 2015

Immersive Engineering program with focus on start-up culture. Had exposure to UX design, growth, and sales.

UC Davis | B.A. Music Theory

Sept 2010 - June 2013

About Me

Always thinking of tech ideas for the future. My passions are creating music, film acting, and traveling the world